漫威影业出品
神盾局特工
第三季 第六集
本字幕由ZiMuZu原创翻译  最新下载请登录www.ZiMuZu.tv
翻译 王大可   苏小黛   杏仁斯嘉丽   香茗小焙   煮粥达人   珈美
翻译 SophiaSaaaga   盐湖嗨爪凉开水   Silence   安sim   西蒙草
时间轴调整 风吹来的那片云后期 宝宝
校对 菲兹草   总监 菲兹-西蒙草
漫威《神盾局特工》前情回顾
Previously on "Marvel's Agents Of S.H.I.E.L.D."...
你为什么想重建传送门  珍玛
Why do you want to rebuild the portal, Jemma?
因为我必须回去
Because I have to get back there.
我们要把他救回来
We're gonna get him back.
我看到了什么
I saw something.
鞭笞能变回人
Lash can turn into a person.
想想看啊  他可能是任何人
I mean, think about it. He could be anybody.
我知道你非常想参与行动  莫尔斯特工
I know you really want to get back into action, agent Morse,
但不行
but the answer's no.
明白  长官
Understood, sir.
如果我不叫我的手下停手
If I don't call off my men,
安德鲁・加纳博士  就死定了
Dr. Andrew Garner, is a dead man.
你只需要放下武器
All you have to do is put your weapons down,
我就放你走
and I'll let you go.
对不起
I'm sorry.
梅特工
Agent May?
他还活着
He's alive.
右肺有气胸可能  给他戴上监测仪
Possible pneumo on the right. Let's get him on the monitor.
他有些脱水  我给他再加一升输液
He's dry. I'm starting him on another liter of fluid.
安德鲁
Andrew...
怎么回事
What happened?
我去商店
I went into the store.
我有点头疼
I...I had a headache.
想买点药
I needed something.
我的一个学生也在
One of my students was there.
是个
Was, uh...
教授
Hey, professor.
你去哪了
Where you been?
转学生
...transfer student.
几周前才开始来上课
He only started a few weeks ago.
跟他一起的还有两个人
Had two men with him.
我也没多少经验
My experience is limited,
但我觉得他们是老手
but I'd say they were professionals.
是九头蛇
It was Hydra.
不知道他们为什么会盯上我
Don't know why they'd be after me.
我知道
I do.
梅  这不是你的错
May, this isn't your fault.
你怎么活下来的
How'd you survive?
菲尔
Phil.
他派了一个神盾局特工跟着我
He had a S.H.I.E.L.D. agent tailing me.
那人救了我的命
The man saved my life.
他让我有时间躲避
He gave me time to find cover,
他的出现也吓了亚历克斯一跳
and he must've caught Alex off guard
因为事情并没有按照他们的计划进行
because nothing went exactly as planned.
那孩子有个打火机
The kid had a lighter.
我艰难地逃到了门口
I barely made to the door.
我一定是被冲击波震到了安全处
The blast must've thrown me clear.
紧接着我就记得看到你  来接我
The next thing I remember, you were there, picking me up.
我真走运
I'm lucky.
难以想象那种情况怎么能有人幸存下来
Can't see how anyone would've survived that.
我知道亚历克斯是个麻烦  但他死了我并不难过
Now, I know Alex is trouble, but I'm not sorry he's gone.
沃德本会逼他杀死我的
Ward would've made him finish the job.
如果沃德...
What if Ward...
他不会的
He won't.
你安全了  有我们呢
You're safe now. We got you.
我们不打扰医生医治你了
We'll let the doctor work on you.
你休息吧
You need to get some rest.
你想去哪
Where the hell do you think you're going?
我想去看看安德鲁
Uh, I think I'm going to see Andrew.
休想
No.
我只想确保他没事
I just want to make sure he's all right.
就是因为你他才有事
You're the reason he's not.
不管怎样沃德都会伤害他的
Ward was gonna hurt him no mat...
-我只是做了最合理的选择  -合理
- I made the most logical choice. - Yeah? Logical?
你是想报仇
You wanted revenge.
科尔森的命令是干掉他
Coulson's orders were to end him.
我有一枪的机会  于是我开枪了
I had one shot. I took it.
而你打偏了  你被撤出任务了
And you missed. You're off that assignment.
很好  那让我去
Good. Then put me on it.
让我去追他
Let me go after him.
你这算归队了吗
Are you back?
对  我归队了
Yeah, I'm back.
神盾局派了个人来暗杀我
S.H.I.E.L.D. sent a man to assassinate me.
他进了我的地盘  还想杀了我
He came into my house and tried to kill me.
就因为你把他放了进来
'cause you let him in.
你大意了
You were sloppy.
我是照你的规矩办事的
I followed your protocol.
他为了接近你不惜杀了个人
He killed a man to get close to you.
他就那么想要你命
He wanted you dead that much.
他们都那么想要我命
They all want me dead that much.
现在还放了个隐患在外面
Now we have a dangling thread.
冯・斯特拉克
Von Strucker.
你就不该派个孩子去做大人的工作
You shouldn't have sent a boy to do a man's job.
总不能指望你装成大学生
Not really sure you'd have blended in
混进去盯住加纳吧
as an undergrad, watching Garner.
冯・斯特拉克有打来吗
Has Von Strucker called in?
那他要么被抓了  被杀了  要么就是跑了
So, he's either captured, killed, or he's running.
只有一种可能性是咱们能接受的
And only one of those options works for us.
那小子知道得太多了
The kid knows too much.
那就赶紧找到他  别被神盾局抢了先
So go and find him before S.H.I.E.L.D. does.
要是他还活着
And if he's still alive...
处理好他
Take care of him.
-你还好吗  -我很生气
- How you holding up? - I'm pissed.
我被鞭笞狠整了一顿
I got manhandled by Lash,
还因此失去了看ATCU机构的机会
and it messed up our chance to see the ATCU facility.
但好消息是  我有个想法
But... good news... I have a theory.
我喜欢想法
I like theories.
鞭笞当时追踪了我们
Lash was tracking us.
他知道我们的车在哪
He knew where our truck was.
这可是内部消息
He... he needed inside info for that.
你觉得他能得到ATCU的情报
You think he's got access to ATCU information?
不  我...
No, I...
我觉得他就是ATCU的人
I think he's in the ATCU.
我们知道他能在怪物和正常人之间
We know that he can transform himself
来回变化
into a regular-sized guy and back.
要是他伪装成了他们的人呢
What if he's hiding out as one of them?
这想法真可怕
That's a scary thought.
我说服罗莎琳带我参观她今天的行动
I've got Rosalind giving me a tour of her operation today.
-让我看看能查到什么  -好
- Let me see what I find there. - Good.
我看看关于鞭笞的身份我能查到什么
I'll see what I can get on Lash's identity.
不管你在调查什么  尽量别惊动到罗莎琳
And whatever you dig into, try to keep it off Rosalind's radar.
我今天需要她相信我
I need her to trust me today.
你不是搞不定她吧
You're not having a hard time working her, are you?
不会太投入了吧
Not getting too attached?
这一行干久了
You do this long enough,
就能学会如何隔绝自己的感情
you learn to cut yourself off from all that.
这样工作更好做
Makes it easier to do the job.
长官
Sir?
梅真的彻底回归了吗
Is May really back for good?
我不确定
I'm not sure.
现在  她想复仇
Right now, she's out for blood.
梅  我听说安德鲁的事了
May, I heard about Andrew.
他怎么样了
How's he...
搞什么
What the hell?!
亨特为了你
Hunter nearly cost Andrew his life,
险些搭上了安德鲁的性命
and he was doing it for you.
我太抱歉了
I-I feel terrible.
你怂恿他
You were egging him on,
让他为你战斗  都是你的错
letting him fight your battles for you. It's your fault!
要是我知道安德鲁会遭遇危险  我绝不会
If I knew Andrew was in danger, I never...
好吧  你不高兴了
Okay. You're upset.
你这不是可以为自己战斗吗
So, you can fight your own battles.
什么
What?
你在考验我
You were testing me?
得确保你可以接任务了
Had to make sure you were mission-ready.
科尔森仍不许我参加作战任务
Coulson still has me off combat duty.
测试表明我的肺仍未痊愈
The tests say that my lung isn't healed all the way yet.
我的测试结果不同
My test says otherwise.
20分钟后出发
Wheels up in 20.
欢迎回来  莫尔斯特工
Welcome back, Agent Morse.
芭比
Bob...
不是你的任务  亨特
Not your mission, Hunter.
离远点  要不然我会让你离远点
Stay away, or I'll make you stay away.
我只想和我前妻说句话
I just want a minute with my ex-wife.
我跟你一起去
I'm going with you.
去你个头
Like hell you are.
你把安德鲁置于险境
You put Andrew at risk.
我都看见沃德了  我当然要开枪了
I had Ward in my sights. Damn right I pulled the trigger.
你是最该能理解的
You of all people should get it.
我能理解
I get it.
你急于诉诸武力  害得一个无辜者受伤
You were quick to violence, and an innocent got hurt.
别人可不像我一样习惯你的行为方式
Other people aren't as used to your behavior as I am.
你什么时候还在乎别人的想法了
Since when do you care what other people think?
你真要回归外勤了吗
You're really going back in the field?
去抓他
After him?
我准备好了
I'm ready.
你在撒谎吗
You lying?
没有
No.
那比我干得好点
Do better than I did, yeah?
你不说那句话吗
You're not gonna say the thing?
你已经知道了
You already know.
有部分细节安德鲁没说对
Andrew didn't get all the details exactly right.
他说现场有四个人
He said there were four men on the scene,
但只找到了三具尸体
but only three bodies were recovered...
科尔森的手下和两个九头蛇的人
Coulson's man, two Hydra guys.
第四个人是安德鲁的一个学生
The fourth guy was one of Andrew's students.
卡尔弗大学  亚历山大・布朗
这是他的身份证  但这是个化名
That's his I.D., but it's an alias.
他不叫亚历山大・布朗
He's not Alexander Braun.
他叫沃纳・冯・斯特拉克
He's Werner Von Strucker.
等等  冯・斯特拉克  就是那个...
Wait. Von Strucker? As in...
九头蛇万岁
Hail Hydra.
沃德在组建自己的小九头蛇王朝
Ward was starting his own little Hydra dynasty.
真可爱
Cute.
我们找到这个斯特拉克小子
We find the Strucker kid,
他会带我们找到沃德
he'll lead us back to Ward.
你有什么办法吗
You got a how?
神盾局一直在监控多个九头蛇的
S.H.I.E.L.D.'s been monitoring several Hydra bank accounts
银行账户
for a while now.
其中一个刚刚有了动静
One just woke up.
开曼群岛
Cayman Islands.
斯特拉克需要钱
Well, Strucker needed funds.
有道理  准备怎么行动
Makes sense. What's the op?
你的普通话怎么样
How's your mandarin?
你觉得呢
如果我们去那里  或许能找到他的踪迹
If we head down there, maybe we'll pick up his trail.
他既要躲沃德  又要躲我们
He's on the run from Ward, from us...
都有点同情这个孩子了
Almost makes me feel sorry for the kid.
他是个怪物
He's a monster.
你叫我来是对的
You were right to ask me to come.
我不知道还能向谁求助
I didn't know where else to turn.
我想你和我父亲
I figured you and my father
肯定经常对付沃德那样的人
must've dealt with guys like Ward all the time.
沃德是个...
Ward is...
我没完成任务
I didn't finish the mission.
他不会在乎原因的
He won't care why.
让一个未受正规训练未经测试的年轻人上场
If you put an untested youth in play without proper training,
这太蠢了
it's foolish.
太令人惊讶了
Boggles the mind, really.
你父亲就明白  保护人才
Your father understood protecting assets
比炫耀他们重要得多
was more important than flaunting them.
他从不让我参与那些事
He never let me in on that stuff.
你对我比他好多了
You were nicer to me than he was.
你父亲是个伟大的人
Your father was a great man.
相信我
Trust me.
换了我们绝不会纵容这种事
We would've never put up with such things.
你不了解这个沃德
You don't know this guy Ward.
他很可怕
He's scary.
我很了解格兰特・沃德
I'm aware of Grant Ward.
他也曾是个未经测试的年轻人
He was once an untested youth, too.
每个人都有过去
Everyone has a history.
那么你会帮我吗
So does that mean you'll help me?
我会处理好一切
I'll handle everything.
-多谢你来接我  -是啊
- Nice of you to pick me up. - Yes.
在街角接  因为你不肯告诉我你的基地在哪
On the corner...since you won't tell me where your base is.
你知道我管理的是情报组织吧
You know I run a spy organization, right?
你也知道我们说好了分享情报  对吗
And you know we agreed to share information, right?
什么事
Yeah?
什么时候
When?
知道是谁吗
Do you know who?
好  让他们开始吧
All right, just have them get started.
我这就来
I'm on my way.
转弯
Turn around.
我们得回去
We need to head back.
好的  夫人
Yes, ma'am.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我得处理一项紧急事务  我们改天再约
It's an emergency I need to handle. We'll reschedule.
现在你该下车了
So, this is the part where you get out of the car.
还是算了
I don't think so.
你不明白是怎么回事吗
Do you not get how this works?
我只知道  我该看看这间机构了
What I get is that it's time to see this facility.
不能再推迟了
No more delays.
我跟你一起走
I'll stay with you.
处理完紧急事务  我们就可以去了
When the emergency's done, then we can go.
不行  我去的地方你不能去
You can't. Not where I'm going.
那我们现在不分享情报了
So we're not sharing information, then?
你刚刚可是把这事看得很重
'Cause you kind of just made a whole thing about that.
好吧
Okay.
科尔森局长会和我们一起去
Director Coulson will be joining us.
带我回家
Take me home.
我就是觉得我能帮上你
I just thought you could use some help.
王舒  凯特琳・芙瑞
我能行  我保证
I've got it. I promise.
我需要集中精力
I just need to concentrate.
是吗
Really?
看上去你的注意力不在这儿呢
Cause it looks like your mind's kind of elsewhere.
传送门模拟就在后台开着
The portal simulation is just running in the background.
我并没分心
They're not taking any of my time.
不代表这就是个好主意
Doesn't make it a good idea.
怎么  你不觉得我该帮助西蒙斯营救威尔吗
What? You don't think I should help Simmons rescue Will?
你觉得该吗  他是你的情敌
Do you think you should? He's the competition.
如果你女朋友的前任要从凤凰城来看她
If your girlfriend's ex wants to visit from Phoenix,
你不会给他买机票吧
you do not buy him a plane ticket.
这比喻真具体
That's really specific.
不管怎么说  这人让西蒙斯活了下来
Anyway, this guy kept Simmons alive.
我欠他的  他值得我去救
I owe him. He deserves my help.
就因为他给了西蒙斯几个月的温暖...
Just because he kept Simmons warm for a few months...
通过生火...
with fire...
不代表你该救他
Doesn't mean he's someone you should save.
你对他了解多少啊
How much do you even know about him?
你在干什么
What're you doing?
我是说  在这里  你为什么在这里
In here, I mean. Why are you here?
科尔森不让我参与行动
Coulson put me on the bench.
我就想着我可以在别处发光发热
So I thought I would offer my expertise elsewhere.
你就取个"凯特琳・芙瑞"
Is that what you're going with... "Katelin Frayer"?
你怎么这么拼"凯特琳"
Is that how you spell "Katelin"?
凯特琳・芙瑞
KAT...
K-a-t...?
这么拼不对吧  伙计
I'm not sure that's right, mate.
嗯  不..."凯特琳"有很多种拼法
Yeah, no, th... there's lots of ways to spell "Katelin."
你能不能找别处
And can you please just find somewhere else
发光发热去
to make yourself useful?
收到
Copy that.
加纳博士  很高兴你起来活动了
Dr. Garner, good to see you up.
有时间做咨询吗
Do you have time for a consult?
天哪  好啊  快说吧
Oh, god, yes, please.
我没想说得那么迫不及待的
That came off more desperate than I intended.
躺着实在太无聊
Being laid up is very boring.
-怎么了  -是关于鞭笞
- What's up? - It's Lash.
-鞭笞  -那个异人杀人恶魔
- Lash? - The inhuman killer monster.
对了  我听说你们打了个照面
Oh, right. I heard you had a run-in with him.
还好你没事
Glad you're okay.
这就是我不理解的地方
That is what I don't understand.
为什么我没事  他专杀异人
Why am I okay? He kills inhumans.
他杀了弗莱  为什么要放过我
He killed Frye. Why spare me?
问得好
That's a tough one.
我还在梳理异人族的心理状态呢
Still trying to put together an inhuman psych profile.
你们都各有特点
You're all different.
是啊  但他...格外独特
Yeah, but he's... Really different.
他变身成了人形  一个普通的人类
He changed into a guy... a regular guy.
你看见他了吗
You saw him?
你有看清楚吗
Did you get a good look at him?
没  只看到个影子  但还是
No, just a shadow, but still...
我都不知道还能这样
I didn't know that was possible.
我也是  但是那家伙那么大又那么丑
Me, either, but someone that big and ugly...
这也合乎逻辑
I mean, it makes sense.
他总得有办法掩人耳目
He's got to get around without being noticed somehow.
林肯说不定能帮上忙呢
Maybe Lincoln can help.
-你知道他在哪吗  -不清楚
- You know where he is? - No idea.
自从ATCU企图抓他  他就失踪了
He's been off the grid since the ATCU tried picking him up,
-但他偶尔会打电话来  -震动女  有空吗
- but he calls sometimes. - Hey, tremors, you got a sec?
是的
Yeah.
谢谢
Thank you.
有消息告诉你
I'll keep you posted.
什么事
What's up?
我在考虑你关于ATCU的假设
Been thinking about your ATCU theory.
谁在护卫队出发前先走了
Now, who took off before the convoy left,
谁知道我们走的路线
and who knew the exact route we were going to take?
班克斯
Banks.
他可以查到ATCU掌握的一切关于异人族的信息
He's got access to everything that ATCU learns about inhumans.
卢瑟・班克斯
我们应该跟踪他
We should tail him.
车已经准备好了  全套监控设备
Already got a van ready to go, full surveillance package.
红外线扫描器  单向玻璃
Infrared scanners, one-way glass...
-太好了  让我准备一下  -我来开车
- Perfect. Let me get some things. - I'll drive.
我是说
I mean...
求你们了
Please.
大开曼岛
王小姐想查看她的保险箱
Ms. Wong would like to access her safe-deposit box.
这是她的帐户号码
Here's her account number.
请出示你们的身份证
I will need your I.D.s, please.
当然
Of course.
希望菲兹没有搞砸
警棍准备好
王小姐说她喜欢你的领带
Ms. Wong likes your tie.
请跟我来
Follow me.
开始了
你们慢慢看  不用着急
Take as much time as you need.
38号箱
Box 38.
菲兹  我们需要斯特拉克的全部信息
Fitz, we need anything on strucker,
能找到沃德的一切线索
anything that will get us to Ward.
收到
Yeah, getting it.
房产证  护照
Real-estate deeds, passport...
没有现金吗
No cash?
他肯定把那些都拿走了  他大概...
He must've cleared it all out. He...
等下  你们好像触动了警报
Oh, uh...Guys, I think you triggered an alarm somewhere.
这可好
Great.
我们还剩多长时间
How much time do we have?
看来没时间了
Looks like zero.
这下糟了
怎么回事
What is happenning in here?
我拿下左边那个
你对付右边那个
经理不成问题
-我老板想祝贺你们  -什么
- My boss would like to congratulate you. - What?
什么
你们的安保系统真是一流
Your security system is top-notch,
团队也很高效
and your team is incredibly efficient.
正如我们的期待
Just what we'd hoped for.
你在跟我开玩笑吗
我们一直在关注你们公司
We've been reading up on you.
我明白你要做什么了  稍等
Oh, I see where you're going with this. One second.
我们想给你们提供一份工作
We'd like to offer you a job.
工作
A job?
这可太不寻常了
This seems most unorthodox.
我们是受你前雇主的托付
We were sent from your former employer,
国家第一信托公司
First Fiduciary National,
他们希望你能回去工作
and they would like you back.
我知道你过得不易  你妻子想回迈阿密
I know it's been hard, your wife missing miami.
你们分居多久了
How long have you been separated?
你怎么知道这个
You know about that?
这真不是一个好主意
你现在的工资只比2012年多4%
You're only earning 4% more than you were in 2012.
我们能让你赚更多
We can do better.
太过分了
我的确一直想换个工作
I... I have been looking to make a change.
你看  这手段不挺好使
他可不觉得
现在  用我的办法吧
不好意思
Sorry.
HTS家庭影院系统
还没来人
No one yet.
班克斯还没回来
Banks still not back.
他37秒前也没回来呢
He wasn't back 37 seconds ago, either,
但是谢谢你的定期提醒
but thanks for the regular updates.
这家伙不是善类
This guy is bad news.
被海军陆战队踢出
Got discharged from the marines.
是有原因的
With cause.
但是罗莎琳还是雇了他
And Rosalind hired him anyway.
纽约一役后  他加入了一支抗外星人精英特遣队
He was part of an Elite Anti-Alien Task Force after New York.
当然了
Of course he was.
他回来后到底有什么计划
So what's the plan when he gets back?
我们要把他抓回去审问吗
Is this a grab-and-torture kind of deal?
如果他是鞭笞  那锁喉大概没用
Chokehold might not work if he turns out to be Lash.
但是我们可以
But we could...
别心急  关塔那摩  你不是只想开车吗
Slow down, Gitmo. I thought you just wanted to drive.
只是给你们点有用的建议
Just offering helpful suggestions.
到底怎么个有用法
Helpful in what way, exactly?
可以阻止坏人吗
Um... stopping bad guys?
不如专业点
How about professionalism?
做事机灵点  别害死人
Doing your job smart, not getting people killed?
大胆猜测一下  你不是在说跟踪班克斯的事吧
Wild guess... this isn't about following Banks.
亨特  安德鲁差点死了
Hunter, come on. Andrew almost died.
说出来了
And there we have it.
我又不是把安德鲁交了出去  然后说
Look, it's not like I just handed over Andrew and said,
杀了我们的朋友吧
"Hey, please kill our friend."
是啊  "我别无选择"
Right. "I had no choice."
我是别无选择
I had no choice.
-我  -先别吵  快看
- I... - Guys, guys.
看来我们要跟着他回家了
Looks like we're following him home.
保持安全距离
At a safe distance!
罗莎琳・普莱斯  ATCU
Rosalind price, ATCU.
是  长官
Yes, ma'am.
抱歉在这种情况下见面
Sorry about the circumstances.
我们会尽力查明闯入者的身份
We'll do our best to make sure we find whoever broke in here.
有人闯进了你家吗
Someone broke into your home?
-有线索吗  -还没
- Any leads? - Not yet.
看来此人被你
Looks like the guy was scared away
惊人的安全系统给吓跑了
by your, uh... very impressive security system.
我们能到处看看吗
All right if we take a look around?
当然
Of course.
你不行
Not you.
这边请
This way.
地方不错啊
Nice place, huh?
从一个女人的藏书能了解她很多事
Can tell a lot about a woman from her books.
好吧  我还真不知道有这么多
Okay, I didn't actually know that there were this many
玛格丽特・撒切尔的传记呢
biographies of Margaret Thatcher.
新家具
New furniture.
崭新的
Brand-new.
老天  你怎么弄到...
Holy... where did you get...
别碰我的东西
Don't touch my things.
抱歉  丢东西了吗
Sorry. Anything missing?
我和警察讲话时你没偷听吗
You weren't listening in when I talked to the cop?
你变迟钝了  菲尔
You're slipping, Phil.
我以为你肯定会想搞些情报呢
I thought you'd definitely be scoping things out.
他打完电话就会回去家里
He's gonna go back inside when he finishes his call.
我们接下来怎么做
What's our next move?
他进了房子  我们今天就什么都做不了了
He goes in his house, we're done for the day.
我还不想放弃
I don't want to give up on him yet.
我可以闯进他车里
I could break into his car,
在速度计上放个针孔摄像头
drop a spot cam in his speedometer.
我们得隐秘一点
We have to be stealthy.
如果他发现你  我们就完了
If he catches you, we're toast.
科尔森正深入虎穴
Coulson is in the belly of the beast.
我们不能让ATCU知道我们在调查他们
We can't tip off the ATCU that we're on to them.
一定有什么办法可以...
There must be some way we can keep...
怎么...
What...
不
Oh, no.
什么情况
What's happening?
不是吧
Come on!
还说要隐秘一点呢
So much for stealthy.
搞定了
Here we go.
这怎么是个好主意了
And this is a good idea how?
我没杀他  我只是冻住了他
I didn't kill him, I-I just iced him.
你还坑了科尔森
And screwed Coulson.
他正在对付罗莎琳  你刚刚射了她二把手
He's working Rosalind, and you just shot her number two.
-等她发现...  -她不会发现的
- When she finds out... - She won't.
我蒙了面
That's what the bandana's for.
鞭笞是异人
Lash is an inhuman.
异人的DNA上有标记
Inhumans have markers in their DNA.
如果我们给班克斯验血查标记
If we test Banks' blood for markers,
就能知道他是不是异人了
we'll know if he's inhuman or not.
还真是个好办法
That's actually kind of smart.
多谢
Thank you.
但我还是觉得你该谈谈你的愤怒问题
But I still think you need to talk about your anger issues.
这里也不是医务室
And this isn't the med lab.
我们没有器具可以采集班克斯的血样
We don't have the equipment to draw Banks' blood.
好吧
Okay.
有血了
There you go... blood.
好吧  我可能有点愤怒问题
Okay, there might be a small anger issue.
把棉签给我
Just pass me the swab.
我只是说你经历了一件很极端的事情
All I'm saying is that you've been through something extreme.
必然会产生后遗症的
There will be after-effects.
这话耳熟吗
Sound familiar?
这样的角色反转真是让人开眼界
It's eye-opening, being on this side of the counseling.
大家小心翼翼地待你
People treat you with kid gloves.
他们是好意  但他们越是想帮忙
They mean well, but the more they try to help...
你越觉得无力
The weaker you feel.
或许是我们的学位的关系
Maybe it's our PhDs.
让他们低估了我们有多么坚强
Makes them underestimate just how strong we really are.
或许吧
Might just be.
抱歉
Excuse me.
黛西
Daisy?
珍玛  我知道你一直没回实验室
Jemma, I know you haven't been in the lab
我也很不想叫你干活儿  但如果
and I hate to ask you to do work, but if...
其实  我能行的
In fact, I can handle it, actually.
不管是做什么
Whatever it is.
你有时间做个血检吗
Do you have time to run a blood analysis?
我想看看班克斯是不是有异人DNA标记
I want to see if Banks has inhuman markers.
我有的是时间  发过来吧
I have plenty of time. Send away.
谢谢  珍玛
Thank you, Jemma.
-有结果告诉你  -好
- I'll call when I know. - Okay.
怎么样
Anything?
他在好事多购物
Guy shops at costco.
有用的信息呢
Anything useful?
连张自拍都没有
There's not even any selfies.
班克斯  你真无趣
Banks, you are boring.
除了他可能是个超级大怪物
Well, apart from the fact that he might be a giant beast
在人胸腔上开洞这一点...
who blows holes in people's chests, but...
不是我  不是我干的
I-I-I didn't do it. I-it wasn't me.
我
I...
我们知道  那是部电话
We know. It's a phone.
"对象正被送往恩德塔克斯"
"Subject en route to Endotex."
没有来电显示
No caller I.D.
盖瑟斯堡的恩德塔克斯实验室吗
Something called Endotex Labs in Gaithersburg?
我们可以去看看  怎么样
We could check it out. What do you think?
西蒙斯拿回结果之前还有时间
Well, we've got time before Simmons comes back with results.
那他呢
What about him?
可以带上他
We could take him with us.
我试过跟鞭笞困在一辆开动的车里
I've been trapped in a moving vehicle with Lash before.
可不想再来一次
Don't love the idea of it happening again.
是啊  如果他有那个DNA标记
Yes, if he has the DNA markers,
我们也知道去哪找他
we know where to find him.
走吧
Let's go.
警方完事了
Cops finished up.
我让我的司机给我们买了汉堡
Had my driver pick up some burgers for us.
我觉得你可能想吃点
Figured you could use some dinner.
街角DJ店的
DJ's from around the corner?
你的电脑还在
So, your computer's still here.
还有两台电视
Couple of TVs, too.
以及挺贵重的艺术品
Some big-time art pieces, I noticed.
不算贵重啦
Hardly big-time.
凑合了
Nice, maybe.
有贼闯进来  却不偷东西  很不寻常啊
Unusual for thieves to break in and not take anything.
我走运吧
Well, lucky me.
-你想说什么吗  -我不知道
- You got a point? - I don't know.
如果你是想挣我的同情分
If you were looking to earn some sympathy from me,
让我心软
soften me up, say,
布置一场闯入也算是个办法
a staged break-in might be one way to do it.
有意思
Interesting.
还有一点也很有意思  我家偏偏
Also interesting, my home had a break-in
在你知道我不在的这天头一次被人闯入了
for the first time ever on the exact day you knew I'd be out.
这指控很严重啊
That's a serious accusation.
你刚刚还指责我假装被闯空门
You just accused me of staging a break-in,
我为什么要这么做呢
which I did why, exactly?
或许我不会喜欢在ATCU机构看到的场面
Maybe I won't like what I see at the ATCU facility,
所以你想让我喜欢你
so you're trying to make me like you.
从雷鸟汽车开始做我工作
Working me ever since the Thunderbird.
显得自己有人情味  让我好接受
Humanizing yourself so I'll take it better.
我真是个疯狂天才啊
I am quite the mad genius, huh?
这些东西真的都是你的吗
Is all this stuff really yours?
我得承认  那根球棒  太聪明了
I got to admit, the bat... that was a nice touch.
三冠王  米奇・曼托
Triple crown winners, autographs from Mickey Mantle,
泰德・威廉姆斯  弗兰克・罗宾逊
Ted Williams, Frank Robinson,
和卡尔・雅泽姆斯基的签名
Carl Yastrzemski?
大部分人看一眼不会知道
Most people just looking at that wouldn't know
那东西价值超过七千  但我知道
that it's worth over 7 grand, but I do.
好了  那球棒不是
Okay, the bat is not...
还有我最喜欢的餐馆DJ店的汉堡
And burgers from my favorite place, DJ's.
ATCU的头头有什么原因
What possible reason would the head of the ATCU have
要用这个留住我
for keeping me here with that?
是啊
You're right.
没有任何原因
No reason at all.
你想去看机构吗
You want to go see the facility?
好啊
Fine.
我们去吧
Let's go see the facility.
好了  每张护照
Okay, each of those passports
都是一个冯・斯特拉克的假身份
has a different fake identity for Von Strucker.
顺说  我的手艺更好
My work is better, just for the record.
-我们知道啦  -嗯
- We know. - Right.
其中一个身份与
Well, one I.D. matches the name
一栋斯特拉克的地产相匹配
on one Strucker real estate holding...
是葡萄牙里斯本的一栋顶层公寓
A penthouse in Lisbon, Portugal.
我检查了一下到达里斯本机场的乘客
So I did a sweep of passengers arriving at the Lisbon airport.
他几小时前通过了海关
He went through customs several hours ago.
干得好  菲兹  谢谢
Nice work, Fitz. Thank you.
不客气
You're welcome.
那我们就去里斯本的那栋顶层公寓
So, we go to a penthouse in Lisbon.
你想谈谈之前银行的事吗
You want to talk about what happened at the bank?
没什么好说的
There's nothing to discuss.
我是把动手当作最后手段
I was treating fighting as a last resort.
这一般是没问题的
Usually, that's good.
一般
Usually.
有时候是因为你害怕
Sometimes it's 'cause you're gun shy.
或许我是没完全恢复  但是是你
Maybe I'm not 100%, but you're the one
不顾测试结果  把我叫来执行任务的
who dragged me on this mission, in spite of the tests.
别拿测试做借口了
Stop hiding behind the tests.
我没有
I'm not.
我说过我想回归外勤
I said I wanted back in the field.
是啊
Sure.
巴林岛一事后  我也说过我讨厌我的小隔间
After Bahrain, I said I hated my cubicle.
但不是真心的
Didn't mean it.
科尔森让你待在基地  你就听了
Coulson says, "Stay home," and you just agree?
你为什么把自己关起来
Why are you keeping yourself locked up?
我去学院找好苗子时  见过你训练的样子
You know, I saw you train at the academy once, scouting you.
我不知道
I didn't know that.
我见过的最厉害的新人
Strongest recruit I ever saw.
任何测试都会表明你当时是满分
Any test would've said you were 100% then.
但你现在更棒了  因为现在你有了经验
But you're better today because now you have experience.
沃德做的事
What Ward did...
你觉得那只是段经历吗
You think that was just experience?
那可以让你更加强大
That can make you stronger.
让它把你变得更强大
Let it.
下次  我们可能就不能靠耍嘴皮子了
'cause next time, talking our way out may not be an option.
手雷
小心点啊
Careful with that one.
我们要是还没搬进来就把这儿炸平可就不好了
Be a shame to see this whole place blow up before we even move in.
你在这儿做什么
What the hell are you doing here?
你不是该出去找冯・斯特拉克的吗
You're supposed to be out looking for Von Strucker.
你是谁
Who is this?
你不知道我是谁
You don't know my name,
但我觉得你一直想引起我的注意
but I think you've been trying to get my attention.
我还想我什么时候能接到你的电话呢
I've been wondering when I'd hear from you.
你就是我出现之前  其他人都怕的人
You're the one all the others were afraid of... before me.
并不是每个人都怕你  沃德先生
Not everyone fears you, Mr. Ward.
不是每个人都该怕我
Well, not everyone should.
只有那些不肯配合的需要怕
Just the ones who won't fall in line.
我能为你做什么
What can I do for you?
不  这个问题不对
No, that's not the correct question.
该问的是  我能给你什么
The correct question is what I can offer you.
如果你想知道  答案是  挽救机会
The answer, in case you're wondering, is redemption.
不了  谢谢  我不需要那个
Oh, no, thanks. I don't need redeeming.
我觉得你需要
Oh, I think you do.
你走错了几招
You made some mistakes in your gameplay,
你拿冯・斯特拉克的儿子当卒子用
using Von Strucker's son as a pawn
而他根本还不该加入
when he shouldn't even be on the board yet.
你瞧  这就是你们那代人的通病
You see, that's just typical of guys in your generation.
你都不知道我使的是什么招
You don't even know the game I'm playing.
冯・斯特拉克可不止是个小卒子
Von Strucker is more than just a pawn.
现在他成了麻烦
And now he's a liability.
他知道太多事了
He knows too much.
我说错了吗
Just tell me if I'm wrong.
你毁了这个人才
You burned that asset.
神盾局在找他  那么你肯定也是
S.H.I.E.L.D. is looking for him, which means so are you.
我知道你在哪可以找到他
And I know where you can find him.
你就准备这么告诉我吗
And you'll just tell me that?
为什么
Why?
有时候得肯牺牲  才能保全大局
Sometimes you sacrifice a player to save the game.
记住  我打给你  就是选择了一边站
You just remember when I come calling that I chose a side.
就是这里
This is the place.
恩德塔克斯的所在地
Matches the Endotex location.
高压镀锌铁丝网  还有虹膜识别
High-voltage, zinc-coated razor wire, iris recognition?
密密麻麻的外围巡逻
Staggered perimeter patrols.
这地方不欢迎外人呢
They don't want any visitors.
肯定是个门面  是吧
It's got to be a front, don't you think?
那怎么办
So what now?
我们出动菲兹新做的探测器
Now we use the new dwarf Fitz crafted.
他觉得这东西还没完成
He doesn't think it's ready yet,
但他是犯傻  这东西帅爆了
but that's stupid because it's awesome, so...
我就给偷来了
I stole it.
怎么了
What?
你不是唯一有点问题的人啊
I didn't say you were the only one with issues.
好了
All right.
西蒙斯  什么结果
Simmons, what do you got?
没有  班克斯没有异人DNA标记
It's negative. Banks has no inhuman markers.
他不是异人
He's not inhuman.
他不是鞭笞喽
So he's not Lash.
不是吧
Really?
我真以为是他呢
I was so sure.
好吧  谢了
Okay. Thanks.
菲兹
Fitz?
我帮完黛西了
I'm done helping Daisy.
既然你也帮完了芭比和梅
And since you're done helping Bobbie and May,
或许现在我们可以看看模拟结果了
I thought maybe now we could take a look at the simulation.
珍玛  我一直想跟你说
Jemma, I've been meaning to say to you...
如果你不乐意帮忙我也完全理解
Look, I understand if you don't want to look into this.
我比你想的坚强
I'm stronger than you think.
不不  珍玛  我研究过了
No, no, no, no, Jemma, I have looked into it.
实际上  我做过几十次模拟了
Actually, I've run dozens of simulations,
而且一直希望能有一次
and I kept on hoping that one of them...
得到结果
would work.
我
I...
我是不想让你失望
I didn't want to disappoint you.
但巨石只是一种选择
The monolith was just one option, though.
我们不会放弃的  好吗
We're not gonna give up, okay?
我知道这对你很艰难
I know this isn't easy for you.
这个状况很奇怪
It's an odd situation.
是啊
Yeah.
简直怪到极点了  即使对我们而言
It's one of the oddest, even for us.
菲兹  如果你认识威尔  你就会理解的
Fitz, if you knew Will, you'd understand.
-我保证  -珍玛  就是这样
- I promise... - Jemma, that's the thing.
我会认识他的
I am gonna know him.
这毫无疑问
It's not even a question.
威尔・丹尼尔斯将带领卫星救援行动  威尔・丹尼尔斯任务概览
家乡英雄威尔・丹尼尔斯
我不管血检结果是什么
I don't care what the blood work says.
那个班克斯很狡猾
That guy Banks is shifty.
他曾把我扣在一辆地铁上
You know he once held me prisoner on a train.
让我很不爽
Didn't care for that.
班克斯还在往这边走
Banks was still on his way here.
恩德塔克斯显然是ATCU的门面
Endotex is obviously a front for ATCU.
里面肯定有问题
No, there's something here.
或许探测器能找到什么
Maybe the dwarf will find something
那样今天也不会白费了
So today won't have been pointless.
班克斯是来送什么东西的
Banks wanted to be here for a delivery of something.
不知道是什么
I wonder what it is.
他们不会看到探测器吗
But won't they see the dwarf?
不会的  这是2.0版的
They will not. That's the 2.0.
菲兹可不该把这东西藏起来呢
Fitz should not be keeping that locked up.
等等  那是什么
Wait a minute, what is that?
我不...
I don't...
安全
Clear.
那是个人吗
Is that a person?
天呐
Oh, god.
他死了吗
Is he dead?
不  他们在监测他  他还活着
No, they're monitoring him. He's alive.
但怎么回事  陷入昏迷了吗
But in some kind of what? A coma?
这是ATCU干的
This is ATCU.
他们在这里存储他们找到的异人
This is where they're storing inhumans they find.
像笼中兽一样
Like animals in cages.
我找个更好的角度
Let me get a better shot.
能调大点声吗  什么都听不到
Can we turn it up? I can't hear a thing.
调大了
It's up.
只能靠这么近了  否则会暴露
This is as close as we can get without giving ourselves away.
背景有杂音
There's noise in the background.
我知道这看上去像什么
I know how it looks.
他应该很震惊才对
He should be freaking out.
这种事应该让人震惊才对
This is the sort of thing that should freak a person out.
他为什么还没有把这里烧成平地啊
Why is he not burning this place to the ground?
他在告诉她他的想法
He... he's telling her what he thinks.
他跟我们一样吓坏了
He's horrified, like we are.
看上去可不像是那样
It doesn't look like it.
把探测器拉回来  别暴露了我们
Look, bring back that dwarf. Make sure we're not discovered.
我们现在不可能再跟ATCU合作了
There's no way we're working with the ATCU now.
震动女
Tremors...
黛西  探测器  撤回来
Daisy, the dwarf... bring it back.
好吧
All right.
是挺有效率
It's efficient, I'll say that.
那是什么  冻结胶质吗
What is it? Some kind of suspension gel?
可以让他们处于静止态  健康鲜活  但沉睡着
It keeps them in stasis... alive, healthy, just asleep.
有件事你说对了
You were right about one thing...
我是不想让你看到
I didn't want to show you.
不是因为我觉得我们做的不对
Not because I think what we're doing here is wrong.
而是因为我知道这看上去多糟
Because I know how it looks.
看上去像恐怖片
Looks like a horror movie.
尽量理解一下
Try to understand,
这些人转化后都深陷麻烦
these people were all in trouble after they turned.
有些人想自残  有些人伤了自己爱的人
Some tried hurting themselves. Some hurt loved ones.
是啊  他们有时很危险  我见识过
Yes, they can be dangerous. I've seen that.
但那也不能...
But it doesn't begin to just...
这东西就像一种疾病
This thing is like an illness.
但我们在寻找解药  而且就要找到了
But we're working on a cure, and we're close...
我们很快就能告诉他们  "你安全了
So close to telling those people, "You're safe.
你爱的人也都安全了
Your loved ones are safe.
你可以回家了"
You can go home."
这就像将人置于药物诱导性昏迷中
It's like putting someone in a medically induced coma
是为了让他们好起来
to make them better.
设想下为一个没有其他选择的人这么做
Imagine doing that for someone who has no other shot.
你失去了一个人
You lost someone.
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
我居然没看出来
I'm such an idiot for not seeing it.
对不起
I'm sorry.
铁杆棒球迷吧
Big baseball fan, I'm guessing.
我丈夫
My husband.
不是因为这个吧
Not to this.
不是
No.
不  那是多年前了
No, it was years ago.
在执行任务时吗
In the field?
不  这就是有趣的地方
No. That's the funny part.
我是出生入死的间谍
I was the spy taking risks.
他是个心脏病学家  老实人
He was a cardiologist, an honest man,
好丈夫  癌症很可恨
a good husband, and cancer sucks.
我很遗憾
I'm sorry.
我愿付出一切  为他做这样的事
I would've given anything to do this for him.
让他睡一会儿
Just put him to sleep for a little while
直到有人能找到解药
until someone found a cure.
我能为他们这么做  为他们的家人
I can do that for those people, for their families.
老实说  我没想到
I got to be honest, I didn't expect...
什么
What?
我也是人吗
That I'm human?
我们可不都是人
Not all of us are.
不完全是人
Not fully.
我完全是
I am.
我觉得你也是的
And I think you are, too.
但如果你敢跟人说我说过这话
But if you tell anyone I said that,
我一定找到你的基地  炸成灰
I'll find your base and blow it up.
这一切让我很难保持自己的人性
I find it hard to keep my humanity in all of this.
一般来说  你得隔绝自己的感情
Usually, you have to cut yourself off from it.
我在尽量不那么做
I'm trying not to.
之前
Before...
你说你觉得我是想要你喜欢我
you said that you thought I wanted you to like me.
是啊  抱歉  那真是
Yeah. Sorry. That was...
但那部分或许
But that part might be a little...
没说错
true.
或许吧
Maybe.
很好
Good.
准备好了吗
Ready?
又是你  好啊
You again. Good.
好吧
All right.
开始了
Here we go.
斯特拉克
Strucker.
沃德在哪
Where do I find Ward?
沃德
Ward...
不
No...
求你
Please...
我干掉过比你壮三倍的男人  丫头
I've taken down men three times your size, girl.
你凭什么觉得自己能打过我
What makes you think you can beat me?
经验
Experience.
我想完成沃德吩咐的任务
I tried to do what Ward wanted.
我想杀了他
I tried to kill him.
他  加纳教授吗
"Him"? Professor Garner.
我们都围住他了
We had him.
但我不知道他会变身
But I didn't know he'd change into that thing.
究竟是怎么回事
What really happened?
这不是真的
That's not true.
他是什么
What is he?
我不知道
I don't know.
《神盾局特工》马上回来
We'll return in a moment.
我说过  你不用担心我
I told you, you don't have to worry about me.
你还好吗  安全吗
Are you all right? Staying safe?
很安全
Safe as houses.
什么
What?
就是个说法而已
It's an expression. People say that.
好啊  等哪天跟我讲讲黑色风暴事件[30年代]
Sure. And someday, you can tell me how you survived the dust bowl
和胡佛政府的故事吧  老爷爷
and the Hoover administration, grandpa.
你嘴巴真刁  黛西
That's an ugly side of you, Daisy.
没办法  你懂规矩
That's too bad. You know the deal.
你说出你在哪  我就不取笑你了
I stop making fun of you when you tell me where you are.
好吧
Yeah.
低调一点  好吗
Just...Keep your head down, okay?
我不希望这东西找到你
I don't want this thing to find you.
你至少还有朋友可找吧
Do you have any friends out there, at least?
没有以前那么多了
Not as many as I used to.
这电话还能打多久就会被你追踪到
How much longer till the call is traceable?
15秒
15 seconds.
我会再联系你的
I'll reach out soon.
希望如此
Hope so.
加纳博士
Dr. Garner, hey.
是林肯吗
Was that Lincoln?
他有什么关于鞭笞的信息吗
He have anything to help us with Lash?
没有  又回到原地了
Nope. Back to square one.
别担心  你很快就能查明白的
Well, don't worry. You'll figure it out soon.
林肯说出自己的位置了吗
Hey, did Lincoln tell you where he is?
他在这里  有我们保护或许更安全
I mean, he'd be safer here, under our protection.
是啊  但他不信我  不肯说
I know, but he doesn't believe me. He won't tell me.
等他说了我会告诉你的
But I'll let you know when he does.
好啊
Great.